

I would like to work at a company, where I could use my previous experiences gained from my early exchange years spent in

Japan and mastered it through practicing programming by creating various projects. I am currently in the field of Full Stack Web Development of HTML, CSS, Javascript and React framework, and Flutter programming languages (possessing intermediate knowledge) and had been coding for 3 years in Python. I am a self-taught developer, who likes challenges, a fast learner, dedicated, well-organized, punctual, open to improvement, and eager to learn new skills and abilities.

PERSONAL DATA

Address: 1182 Budapest, Törökbálint street 16/b

Phone number: +3670/3197-548 Email: eckertjozsef5@gmail.com Date of Birth: 12th of November 1991 Github: https://github.com/Joeworker11

https://www.linkedin.com/in/j%C3%B3zsef-eckert-

21077a161/

SPOKEN LANGUAGES

Hungarian - native language

English - superlative degree(advanced

level - C1 - active)

Japanese - advanced level (JLPT N1) active

- Business Japanese (Keigo)
- Japanese (Kansai dialect)
- Okinawan Japanese

Chinese - HSK4 level(written), HSK2 level (speaking) studying active

German - beginner level - inactive

JÓZSEF ECKERT

WORK EXPERIENCE

Japanese-Hungarian interpreter technical translator (freelancing)

Toyo Ink Hungary co. Ltd. | March 2021 - September 2022

- interpreting in the territory of the factory(conferences, board meetings, working with engineers at the production area)
- translating technical documentation in the office concerning factory rules, product quality, quantity, manufacturing, instruction sheets, etc.

Japanese-English-Hungarian interpreter and technical translator, HR & GA Staff

Taiho Corporation Of Europe Kft. | September 2019 - March 2021

Japanese-English-Hungarian all kind of translation and interpretation - HR & GA Staff member (regular 5S on-site check, kaizen and 5S evaluations, preparing analyses and reports, kaizen bonuses and administration; payrolling the car fuel alowance; handing over safety equipments; administration; supply; writing internal & external purchase orders; communicating with the suppliers; monitoring price changes of purchase orders; organizing and conducting on-site meetings, preparing related statistics and reports; handling invoices)

Japanese-English-Hungarian interpreter and technical translator, Assistant Manager

Eckert Művek Kft. | August 2018 - August 2019

- interpreting and translating in Japanese-English-Hungarian (venetian blinds, roll-top, building trade terminology)
- administration (creating documents such as tenders, budgets, technical proposals, contracts in Microsoft Word and Excel)
- customer service (via email)
- supply
- writing the content of the website

Japanese-Hungarian interpreter and technical translator

NHK Spring Hungary Kft. | September 2016 - August 2017

- interpreting in the territory of the factory
- translating technical documentations in the office concerning the rules of the factory, product quality and quantity, manufacturing, instruction sheets etc.

Office Assistant

- TNT EXPRESS Hungary Kft | January 2014 July 2015 communication with partners in both English and Hungarian (through email)
- administrative works
- handling and stock taking about the incoming and outgoing packets

OTHER PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Tech Skills:

- Python
- HTML5, CSS (Tailwind,

Bootstrap)

- Javascript
- React
- C++
- GitHub
- Git bash
- -Flutter-Dart(Web, Android)
- Microsoft Office
- BMD (intermediate)
- Figma

Driving Licence:

Category B since 2009 - active driving skills (300 000 km)

Other pieces of knowledge, and experiences:

- fast typing
- Japanese speech contest winner
 (University of the Ryukyus 2016) good presentational skills

INTEREST, HOBBIES

- studying new languages
- attending events concerning Asian cultures
- self-improvement in web development and programming(mastering databases such: as NodeJS, MongoDB, and SQL) -learning new frameworks: Angular, NextJS, ThreeJS reading books about
- reading books about psychology, martial arts, sci-fi, adventure, etc.

TEMPORARY WORKS

Japanese - Hungarian moderator
 Okinawa- Mi amor photo exhibition

Hungarian Natural History Museum | 24th of August 2018

Japanese - Hungarian moderator
 The 30th Anniversary of the Hungary-Japan

 Friendship Society

Museum of Ethnography | 27th of October 2017

Japanese - Hungarian moderator

Japanese Days

Ferenc Hopp Museum of Asiatic Arts | 12-13rd of May 2017 and 25th of May 2018

Presenting the upcoming events, speeches and performances, reviewing the organized programs or invited guests. Accompanying to the Japanese Ambassador and interpreting, when it was needed.

Takenaka Europe GmbH | 20th of April - 30th of May 2017
 Typing and correcting an HR manual in Japanese.

EDUCATION

Prooktatás

October 2022 - August 2023

Full Stack Web Development

Károli Gáspár University of the Reformed Church in Hungary

September 2016 - June 2018

Japanese Studies (Master's Degree) Philologist in Japanese Studies

Károli Gáspár University of the Reformed Church in Hungary

September 2012 - June 2015

Bachelor's Degree in Japanese Studies Expert in Oriental Languages and Cultures

Karl Gundel Secondary School of Catering and Tourism

September 2006 - June 2012

EXCHANGE YEARS, FURTHER EXPERIENCES

University of the Ryukyus (琉球大学)

September 2015 - September 2016

Japan, Okinawa prefecture, Nishihara city MEXT Japanese Studies Scholarship

Shibata Central High School (新発田中央高等学校

March 2010 - February

Japan, Niigata prefecture, Shibata city 2011 AFS exchange year